Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation Records UA042
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Surveys and reports, 1900 -- 2007; 1965 -- 1999; UA042.001; 56.4 Linear Feet; 139 Digital Object(s)
  - Staff Survey of Clinical Operations, 1999; UA042.001.058.00005 (Box 58)
  - Standards for Accredidation, 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.058.00006 (Box 58)
  - Stonebridge Survey, 2000 -- 2001; UA042.001.058.00007 (Box 58)
  - Strategic Planning Survey, 1999; UA042.001.058.00008 (Box 58)
  - Strategic Review, 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.058.00009 (Box 58)
  - Strategic Plan 1986 - 1989, 1987; UA042.001.058.00010 (Box 58)
  - Strategic Plan, 1982 -- 1986; UA042.001.058.00011 (Box 58)
  - Strategic Plan, 1999 -- 2003; UA042.001.058.00012 (Box 58)
  - Strategic Plan 91 - 92 Task Force on Conditions, 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.058.00013 (Box 58)
  - Student Charges Comparative Info 90 - 91, 1990; UA042.001.058.00014 (Box 58)
  - Student Financial Resources Corporation Survey, 1991; UA042.001.058.00015 (Box 58)
  - Student Indebtedness, 1989; UA042.001.058.00016 (Box 58)
  - Student Loans - Canada, 1995; UA042.001.058.00017 (Box 58)
  - Survey Design, Scanning Info, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.058.00018 (Box 58)
  - Survey of Voluntary Support of Education, 1988 -- 1989; UA042.001.058.00019 (Box 58)
  - Medford Campus Planning Task Force, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.058.00020 (Box 58)
  - TCU, 1994; UA042.001.058.00021 (Box 58)
  - Tisch Library, 1999 -- 2001; UA042.001.058.00022 (Box 58)
  - Time to Degree Calder Report, 1996; UA042.001.058.00023 (Box 58)
  - TOPS, 1994; UA042.001.058.00024 (Box 58)
  - Transfer Student Info '91 - '96, 1996; UA042.001.058.00025 (Box 58)
  - Tufts Chemistry Survey, 1997; UA042.001.058.00026 (Box 58)
  - Tufts Orientation Survey [1 of 4], 1999; UA042.001.058.00027 (Box 58)
  - Tufts Orientation Survey [2 of 4], 1999; UA042.001.058.00028 (Box 58)
  - Tufts Orientation Survey [3 of 4], 1999; UA042.001.058.00029 (Box 58)
  - Tufts Orientation Survey [4 of 4], 1999; UA042.001.058.00030 (Box 58)
  - Tufts University Campus Tour Evaluation, 1993; UA042.001.058.00031 (Box 58)
  - Tuition and Fees Misc. Info, 1989 -- 1990; UA042.001.058.00032 (Box 58)
  - Tuition Remission [1 of 8], 1992; UA042.001.058.00033 (Box 58)
  - Tuition Remission [2 of 8], 1990 -- 1992; UA042.001.058.00034 (Box 58)
  - Tuition Remission [3 of 8], 1990 -- 1992; UA042.001.058.00035 (Box 58)
  - Tuition Remission [4 of 8], 1990 -- 1992; UA042.001.058.00036 (Box 58)
  - Tuition Remission [5 of 8], 1992; UA042.001.058.00037 (Box 58)
  - Tuition Remission [6 of 8], 1992; UA042.001.058.00038 (Box 58)
  - Tuition Remission [7 of 8], 1992; UA042.001.058.00039 (Box 58)
  - Tuition Remission [8 of 8], 1992; UA042.001.058.00040 (Box 58)
  - TUSDM Patient Satisfaction Survey 1996 - 1997, UA042.001.059.00001 (Box 59)
  - TUSDM Survey of Professional Attitudes and Care, 1998; UA042.001.059.00002 (Box 59)
  - TUSVM Animal Experience Interest Survey - Levine, 1997; UA042.001.059.00003 (Box 59)
  - TUSVM Outcomes Assessment, 1995; UA042.001.059.00004 (Box 59)
  - TUSVM Assessment, 1999; UA042.001.059.00005 (Box 59)
  - TUSVM Entering and Exiting Student Survey Trends, 1999; UA042.001.059.00006 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 - Bob Gawlak Project, 1995; UA042.001.059.00007 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 Budget Follow-up Report, 1996; UA042.001.059.00008 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 Budget Office [binder], 1995; UA042.001.059.00009 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 - Carol Marshall, 1995; UA042.001.059.00010 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 Development, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.059.00011 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 Development Survey Data Analysis, 1996; UA042.001.059.00012 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 - Grafton Benefits, 1995; UA042.001.059.00013 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 New Hire Orientation Survey, 1996; UA042.001.059.00014 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 Pre-Health, 1995; UA042.001.059.00015 (Box 59)
  - TQ3 Recruitment, 1996; UA042.001.059.00016 (Box 59)
  - Undegraduate Admissions, 1979; UA042.001.059.00017 (Box 59)
  - Undergraduate Admissions Survey Report, 1981; UA042.001.059.00018 (Box 59)
  - V'98 Entering Survey, 1994; UA042.001.059.00019 (Box 59)
  - V'97 Exiting, 1997; UA042.001.059.00020 (Box 59)
  - V'99 Entering Survey, 1995; UA042.001.059.00021 (Box 59)
  - Validity Studies, 1967; UA042.001.059.00022 (Box 59)
  - Validity Study Service, 1966; UA042.001.059.00023 (Box 59)
  - Validity Study Service, 1978; UA042.001.059.00024 (Box 59)
  - Validity Study Service, 1980; UA042.001.059.00025 (Box 59)
  - Validity Study Service, 1981; UA042.001.059.00026 (Box 59)
  - Validity Study Service, 1982; UA042.001.059.00027 (Box 59)
  - Validity Study Service, 1984; UA042.001.059.00028 (Box 59)
  - Vet exiting, 2000; UA042.001.060.00001 (Box 60)
  - Vet Merge Pre-Vet Study, 1993; UA042.001.060.00002 (Box 60)
  - Vet School Survey, Drafts with Style Sheet, UA042.001.060.00003 (Box 60)
  - Visitor Survey and Data [1 of 3], 1999; UA042.001.060.00004 (Box 60)
  - Visitor Survey and Data [2 of 3], 1999; UA042.001.060.00005 (Box 60)
  - Visitor Survey and Data [3 of 3], 1999; UA042.001.060.00006 (Box 60)
  - Voluntary Support of Education, CFAE 92 - 94, 1994; UA042.001.060.00007 (Box 60)
  - Women in Engineering Project, 1995; UA042.001.060.00008 (Box 60)
  - Worker's Comp, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.060.00009 (Box 60)
    - Worker's Compensation Survey, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.060.00009.00001
  - Zemsky Transcript Study, 1989; UA042.001.060.00010 (Box 60)
  - ASE 2002 Enrollment by Race and Faculty Stats, UA042.001.060.00011 (Box 60)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey, 1993; UA042.001.060.00012 (Box 60)
  - ACE, 1997 -- 2001; UA042.001.060.00013 (Box 60)
  - Admissions New Student Survey 2001, UA042.001.060.00014 (Box 60)
  - Alumni Survey 1999 - 2000 Classes of '89 and '94 [binder], UA042.001.060.00015 (Box 60)
  - Alumni Survey Class of 1952, 2001 -- 2002; UA042.001.060.00016 (Box 60)
  - College Newslink Evaluation, 1998; UA042.001.060.00017 (Box 60)
  - Dental Admissions 1984 - A Report on a Survey of Applicants to the Class of 1988, UA042.001.060.00018 (Box 60)
  - Dental Admissions, 2000; UA042.001.060.00019 (Box 60)
  - Dental Admissions 2003, 2004; UA042.001.060.00020 (Box 60)
  - Dental Admissions, 2006; UA042.001.060.00021 (Box 60)
  - Dental Patient Record Audit Spring Summer, 2000; UA042.001.060.00022 (Box 60)
  - Dental Recent Graduate 2000, UA042.001.060.00023 (Box 60)
  - Dining Services Survey 2000, 2001; UA042.001.060.00024 (Box 60)
  - Engineering Senior Survey, 2003; UA042.001.060.00025 (Box 60)
  - Enrollment Study Graduate 1991 - 2000, 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.060.00026 (Box 60)
  - Facilities Survey 2000, UA042.001.060.00027 (Box 60)
  - Financial Aid Retention Data, 1997; UA042.001.060.00028 (Box 60)
  - Financial Aid Retention Data, 1996; UA042.001.060.00029 (Box 60)
  - Financial Aid Awarded First Year, 1990; UA042.001.060.00030 (Box 60)
  - Financial Aid Reply 1993, Class of 1997, UA042.001.060.00031 (Box 60)
  - Finanical Aid Reply Form, 1994; UA042.001.060.00032 (Box 60)
  - Financial Aid Survey, 1992; UA042.001.060.00033 (Box 60)
  - Fletcher Admissions Survey for Enrolled Students, Non-Enrolled Students, and the Fletcher Inquiry Survey, 2001; UA042.001.061.00001 (Box 61)
    - Fletcher Inquiry/New Student/Non-Enrolled Files, 2001; UA042.001.061.00001.00001
  - Fletcher School Existing Student Survey, 2000; UA042.001.061.00002 (Box 61)
  - Grad Schools Attended Black-Historic, 2000; UA042.001.061.00003 (Box 61)
  - HEDS Comparative Sr. Survey, 2003; UA042.001.061.00004 (Box 61)
  - Hughes Biology Seminars & Tufts Biosience Summer Research Program, 2001; UA042.001.061.00005 (Box 61)
    - Hughes Biology Seminars, 2001; UA042.001.061.00005.00001
  - Inquiry, 1995 -- 2000; UA042.001.061.00006 (Box 61)
    - Inquiry, 1995 -- 2000; UA042.001.061.00006.00001
  - Inquiry Comment Codes, 1998; UA042.001.061.00007 (Box 61)
  - Major Advising Report 1 of 3 Engineering [binder], 2003; UA042.001.061.00008 (Box 61)
  - Major Advising Report 2 of 3 Liberal Arts [binder], 2003; UA042.001.061.00009 (Box 61)
  - Major Advising Report 3 of 3 Liberal Arts [binder], 2003; UA042.001.061.00010 (Box 61)
  - Major Advising 1 of 3 Engingeering [binder], 2002; UA042.001.061.00011 (Box 61)
  - Major Advising 2 of 3 Liberal Arts [binder], 2002; UA042.001.061.00012 (Box 61)
  - Major Advising 3 of 3 Liberal Arts [binder], 2002; UA042.001.061.00013 (Box 61)
  - Major Evaluation Report [binder] [1 of 2], 2001; UA042.001.061.00014 (Box 61)
  - Major Evaluation Report [binder] [2 of 2], 2001; UA042.001.061.00015 (Box 61)
  - Matric. Students Finance Graphs, 2000; UA042.001.061.00016 (Box 61)
  - Mobile Technology Cart Users, 2000; UA042.001.061.00017 (Box 61)
  - NEAIR Paper, 2001; UA042.001.061.00018 (Box 61)
  - New Student Labels (back) New Student Comment Codes, 1999; UA042.001.061.00019 (Box 61)
  - NPSAS Update, 1990; UA042.001.061.00020 (Box 61)
  - Orientation Survey First Year and Transfer Students, 1999; UA042.001.061.00021 (Box 61)
    - Orientation Access Database, 1999; UA042.001.061.00021.00001
  - Orientation Survey First Year and Transfer Students, 1995 -- 2000; UA042.001.061.00022 (Box 61)
    - Orientation, 1995 -- 2000; UA042.001.061.00022.00001
  - Pre-Major Advising Art History - Music [binder], 1998; UA042.001.061.00023 (Box 61)
  - Pre-Major Advising Philosophy - Mechanical Engineering [binder], 1998; UA042.001.061.00024 (Box 61)
  - Pre-Major Advising Survey [binder], 1996; UA042.001.061.00025 (Box 61)
  - Pre-Vet Study, 1990; UA042.001.061.00026 (Box 61)
  - Public Safety on the Grafton Campus, 1999; UA042.001.062.00001 (Box 62)
  - Public Safety Survey, 2002 -- 2003; UA042.001.062.00002 (Box 62)
  - Putting Together the Higher Education Puzzle (1 of 2), 1997; UA042.001.062.00003 (Box 62)
  - Putting Together the Higher Education Puzzle (2 of 2), 1999; UA042.001.062.00004 (Box 62)
  - REAL 30th Anniversary Alumni Survey, 2000; UA042.001.062.00005 (Box 62)
  - REAL Students, 1999; UA042.001.062.00006 (Box 62)
  - Religious Preferences, 2001; UA042.001.062.00007 (Box 62)
  - Religious Preferences of Entering Students, 1996 -- 2000; UA042.001.062.00008 (Box 62)
  - School of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Association Survey, 2000; UA042.001.062.00009 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (2) [binder] 1 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00010 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (2) [binder] 2 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00011 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (2) [binder] 3 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00012 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (2) [binder] 4 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00013 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (3) [binder] 1 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00014 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (3) [binder] 2 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00015 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (3) [binder] 3 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00016 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (3) [binder] 4 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00017 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (1) [binder] 1 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00018 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (1) [binder] 2 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00019 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (1) [binder] 3 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00020 (Box 62)
  - Senior Survey (1) [binder] 4 of 4, 2003; UA042.001.062.00021 (Box 62)
  - Sophomore Survey [binder], 1999; UA042.001.062.00022 (Box 62)
  - Sophomore Survey Electronic Media [binder], 1999; UA042.001.062.00023 (Box 62)
    - Preview Eng, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00001
    - English, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00002
    - Engineering Faculty Tables - Chemical, Civil, Electrical, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00003
    - Pre-Major Advising Access Data, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00004
    - Pre-Major Advising University Report, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00005
    - Faculty Tables - Anthropology, Sociology, Computer Science, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00006
    - Faculty Tables - Art History, Biology, Child Development, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00007
    - Faculty Tables - Chemistry, Classics, Drama, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00008
    - Faculty Tables - Economics, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00009
    - Faculty Tables - Geology, German, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00010
    - Faculty Tables - History, Math, Music, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00011
    - Faculty Tables - Music, Philosophy, Physics, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00012
    - Faculty Tables - Political Science, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00013
    - Music (continued), 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00014
    - Faculty Tables - Psychology, Romance Languages, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00015
    - Pre-Major Advising Staff (continued), 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00016
    - Engineering Faculty Tables - Mechanical, 1999; UA042.001.062.00023.00017
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] 1 of 3, 2000; UA042.001.062.00024 (Box 62)
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] 2 of 3, 2000; UA042.001.063.00001 (Box 63)
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] 3 of 3, 2000; UA042.001.063.00002 (Box 63)
  - Pre-Major Advising Engineering, 2002; UA042.001.063.00003 (Box 63)
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] (1 of 2), 2001; UA042.001.063.00004 (Box 63)
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] (2 of 2), 2004; UA042.001.063.00005 (Box 63)
    - Sophomore Survey - IDs Stripped, 2004; UA042.001.063.00005.00001
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] (1 of 2), 2002; UA042.001.063.00006 (Box 63)
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] (2 of 2), 2002; UA042.001.063.00007 (Box 63)
    - Pre-Major Engineering Advising Report, 2002; UA042.001.063.00007.00001
    - Sophomore Survey - No IDs, 2002; UA042.001.063.00007.00002
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] (1 of 3), 2003; UA042.001.063.00008 (Box 63)
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] (2 of 3), 2003; UA042.001.063.00009 (Box 63)
  - Sophomore Survey [binder] (3 of 3), 1998 -- 2003; UA042.001.063.00010 (Box 63)
    - Sophomore Survey, 1998 -- 2003; UA042.001.063.00010.00001
    - 1st Year Pre-Major Advising, 2003; UA042.001.063.00010.00002
    - Sophomore Engineering, 2003; UA042.001.063.00010.00003
  - Substance Abuse, 1988; UA042.001.063.00011 (Box 63)
  - Teaching Goal Requests, 1995; UA042.001.063.00012 (Box 63)
  - Technology Use Survey for Faculty, 2000; UA042.001.063.00013 (Box 63)
    - TUSDM Technology Use Survey, 2000; UA042.001.063.00013.00001
  - Tisch Library Survey, 1999; UA042.001.063.00014 (Box 63)
  - Tisch Library Survey, 2000; UA042.001.063.00015 (Box 63)
  - Tisch Library Survey, 2001; UA042.001.063.00016 (Box 63)
  - Tufts Dining Service Survey, 2001; UA042.001.063.00017 (Box 63)
    - Dining Services, 2001; UA042.001.063.00017.00001
  - Tufts Dining Services Survey for Off-Campus Juniors and Seniors, 2002; UA042.001.063.00018 (Box 63)
    - Dining Off-Campus Juniors and Seniors Survey Fall, 2002; UA042.001.063.00018.00001
  - Tufts University GSAS Exit Survey, 1997 -- 2001; UA042.001.063.00019 (Box 63)
    - GSAS Exit Survey, 1997 -- 2001; UA042.001.063.00019.00001
  - Tufts University Joint Peer Leader Training Program Orientation, 1999; UA042.001.063.00020 (Box 63)
  - Tufts University Task Force on the Undergraduate Experience Faculty Survey, 2002; UA042.001.063.00021 (Box 63)
  - TUSDM Summer Research Program, 2001; UA042.001.063.00022 (Box 63)
  - TUSVM Alumni/Alumnae Survey, 1994; UA042.001.063.00023 (Box 63)
  - TUSVM Alumni/Alumnae Survey, 1999; UA042.001.063.00024 (Box 63)
    - Vet Alumni, 1999; UA042.001.063.00024.00001
  - Tufts Animal Expo Exhibitor Evaluation, 2000; UA042.001.064.00001 (Box 64)
  - TUSVM Computer Use Questionnaire, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.064.00002 (Box 64)
  - TUSVM Employer Survey, 2000; UA042.001.064.00003 (Box 64)
  - TUSVM Faculty Survey Comparative Results, 1994; UA042.001.064.00004 (Box 64)
    - TUSVM Faculty Survey, 1994; UA042.001.064.00004.00001
  - TUSVM Fourth Year Clinical Assessment, 1995; UA042.001.064.00005 (Box 64)
    - TUSVM Clinical Assessment, 1995; UA042.001.064.00005.00001
  - V'2000 Entering Preview, 1996; UA042.001.064.00006 (Box 64)
  - V'2000 Entering Comments, 1996; UA042.001.064.00007 (Box 64)
  - V'2000 Entering, 1996; UA042.001.064.00008 (Box 64)
  - V'2001 Entering, 1997; UA042.001.064.00009 (Box 64)
  - V'2002 Entering, 1998; UA042.001.064.00010 (Box 64)
  - V 2001 Exiting, 1994 -- 2001; UA042.001.064.00011 (Box 64)
    - Vet Exiting, 1994 -- 2001; UA042.001.064.00011.00001
  - Vet Exiting, 2002; UA042.001.064.00012 (Box 64)
  - National Science Foundation Visit, 1989; UA042.001.064.00013 (Box 64)
  - Vet Expo, 2001; UA042.001.064.00014 (Box 64)
    - Vet Expo, 2001; UA042.001.064.00014.00001
  - Vet Expo, 2002; UA042.001.064.00015 (Box 64)
    - Vet Expo, 2002; UA042.001.064.00015.00001
  - Web Survey Hosting Sites, 2001; UA042.001.064.00016 (Box 64)
  - 4 Year Comparison, 1988 -- 1992; UA042.001.065.00001 (Box 65)
  - AA '96 [1 of 2, binder 1 of 3], 1996; UA042.001.065.00002 (Box 65)
  - AA '96 [1 of 2, binder 2 of 3], 1996; UA042.001.065.00003 (Box 65)
  - AA '96 [1 of 2, binder 3 of 3], 1996; UA042.001.065.00004 (Box 65)
  - AA '96 [2 of 2, binder 1 of 2], 1996; UA042.001.065.00005 (Box 65)
  - AA '96 [2 of 2, binder 2 of 2], 1996; UA042.001.065.00006 (Box 65)
  - AA '97 [Binder 1 of 3], 1997; UA042.001.065.00007 (Box 65)
  - AA '97 [Binder 2 of 3], 1997; UA042.001.065.00008 (Box 65)
  - AA '97 [Binder 3 of 3], 1997; UA042.001.065.00009 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Final Report [Binder 1 of 3, Book 1 of 2], 2000; UA042.001.065.00010 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Final Report [Binder 2 of 3, Book 1 of 2], 2000; UA042.001.065.00011 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Final Report [Binder 3 of 3, Book 1 of 2], 2000; UA042.001.065.00012 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Final Report [Binder 1 of 3, Book 2 of 2], 2000; UA042.001.065.00013 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Final Report [Binder 2 of 3, Book 2 of 2], 2000; UA042.001.065.00014 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Final Report [Binder 3 of 3, Book 2 of 2], 2000; UA042.001.065.00015 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study [Binder 1 of 3], 2001; UA042.001.065.00016 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study [Binder 2 of 3], 2001; UA042.001.065.00017 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study [Binder 3 of 3], 2001; UA042.001.065.00018 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Final Report [Binder 1 of 3], 2002; UA042.001.065.00019 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Final Report [Binder 2 of 3], 2002; UA042.001.065.00020 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Final Report [Binder 3 of 3], 2002; UA042.001.065.00021 (Box 65)
  - Accepted Applicants Study Final Report [Binder 1 of 2], 2002; UA042.001.066.00001 (Box 66)
  - Accepted Applicants Study Final Report [Binder 2 of 2], 2002; UA042.001.066.00002 (Box 66)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Preliminary Report [Binder 1 of 5], 1996; UA042.001.066.00003 (Box 66)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Preliminary Report [Binder 2 of 5], 1996; UA042.001.066.00004 (Box 66)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Preliminary Report [Binder 3 of 5], 1996; UA042.001.066.00005 (Box 66)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Preliminary Report [Binder 4 of 5], 1996; UA042.001.066.00006 (Box 66)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Preliminary Report [Binder 5 of 5], 1996; UA042.001.066.00007 (Box 66)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Preliminary Report Book 2 Variable by Race and Financial Aid [Binder 1 of 2], 1998; UA042.001.066.00008 (Box 66)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Preliminary Report Book 2 Variable by Race and Financial Aid [Binder 2 of 2], 1998; UA042.001.066.00009 (Box 66)
  - Admissions Inquiry [Binder 1 of 3], 2002; UA042.001.066.00010 (Box 66)
  - Admissions Inquiry [Binder 2 of 3], 2002; UA042.001.066.00011 (Box 66)
  - Admissions Inquiry [Binder 3 of 3], 2002; UA042.001.066.00012 (Box 66)
  - Admissions Inquiry [Binder 1 of 3], 2003; UA042.001.066.00013 (Box 66)
  - Admissions Inquiry [Binder 2 of 3], 2003; UA042.001.066.00014 (Box 66)
  - Admissions Inquiry [Binder 3 of 3], 2003; UA042.001.066.00015 (Box 66)
  - AMCAS Historical 2001 - 2005 Reports and Graphs [Binder 1 of 3], 2006; UA042.001.066.00016 (Box 66)
  - AMCAS Historical 2001 - 2005 Reports and Graphs [Binder 2 of 3], 2006; UA042.001.066.00017 (Box 66)
  - AMCAS Historical 2001 - 2005 Reports and Graphs [Binder 3 of 3], 2006; UA042.001.066.00018 (Box 66)
  - AMCAS Historical 2001 - 2004 Reports and Graphs [Binder 1 of 3], 2005; UA042.001.066.00019 (Box 66)
  - AMCAS Historical 2001 - 2004 Reports and Graphs [Binder 2 of 3], 2005; UA042.001.066.00020 (Box 66)
  - AMCAS Historical 2001 - 2004 Reports and Graphs [Binder 3 of 3], 2005; UA042.001.066.00021 (Box 66)
  - AMCAS Report Graphs [Binder], 2001; UA042.001.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - AMCAS Report Graphs Data [Binder], 2002; UA042.001.067.00002 (Box 67)
    - AMCAS Data, 2002; UA042.001.067.00002.00001
  - Athletics Report Seniors '99 '00, 2000; UA042.001.067.00003 (Box 67)
  - Attrition Retention Rates Class of '82, 1983; UA042.001.067.00004 (Box 67)
  - Attrition Retention Rates Engineering Class of 1986, 1984; UA042.001.067.00005 (Box 67)
  - Calder Foundation Proposal, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.067.00006 (Box 67)
    - Calder - Data for Those Graduating, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.067.00006.00001
  - Correspondence Dawn G. Terkla, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.067.00007 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence Dawn G. Terkla, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.067.00008 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence Dawn G. Terkla, 1994; UA042.001.067.00009 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence Dawn G. Terkla, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.067.00010 (Box 67)
  - Department Budgets, 2004; UA042.001.067.00011 (Box 67)
  - Differential Housing Study Update, 1986; UA042.001.067.00012 (Box 67)
  - Director of Analytic Studies, 1981; UA042.001.067.00013 (Box 67)
  - Electronic Medical Records TUSVM, 1998; UA042.001.067.00014 (Box 67)
  - Enrollment Data - Engineering, 1997; UA042.001.067.00015 (Box 67)
  - Enrollment Data 1991 - 1992, 1996 - 1997, 1996 -- 1998; UA042.001.067.00016 (Box 67)
  - Graduate School, 1996 -- 1999; UA042.001.067.00017 (Box 67)
  - Grants and Contracts Survey, 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.067.00018 (Box 67)
  - HEDS Retention, 1988 -- 1999; UA042.001.067.00019 (Box 67)
  - HEDS Senior Survey, 1997; UA042.001.067.00020 (Box 67)
  - Housing Survey Development, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.067.00021 (Box 67)
  - Housing Survey at Selected Institutions, 1989; UA042.001.067.00022 (Box 67)
  - Institutional Self Study Summary Tufts University School of Medicine, 2006; UA042.001.067.00023 (Box 67)
  - LCME Site Visit, 2005 -- 2006; UA042.001.067.00024 (Box 67)
  - Matriculant, Non-Matriculant Final Report Book 1 [Binder 1 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.067.00025 (Box 67)
  - Matriculant, Non-Matriculant Final Report Book 1 [Binder 2 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.067.00026 (Box 67)
  - Matriculant, Non-Matriculant Final Report Book 1 [Binder 3 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.067.00027 (Box 67)
  - Matriculant, Non-Matriculant Final Report Book 2 [Binder 1 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.067.00028 (Box 67)
  - Matriculant, Non-Matriculant Final Report Book 2 [Binder 2 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.067.00029 (Box 67)
  - Matriculant, Non-Matriculant Final Report Book 2 [Binder 3 of 3], 1998; UA042.001.067.00030 (Box 67)
  - MCAS Data/Report/Graphs [Binder 1 of 3], 2000; UA042.001.068.00001 (Box 68)
  - MCAS Data/Report/Graphs [Binder 2 of 3], 2000; UA042.001.068.00002 (Box 68)
  - MCAS Data/Report/Graphs [Binder 3 of 3], 2000; UA042.001.068.00003 (Box 68)
  - Medical Accreditation, 2004; UA042.001.068.00004 (Box 68)
  - Memorandum - Class of 1995 Comparisons with Peer Institutions, 1996; UA042.001.068.00005 (Box 68)
  - Medical Student Analysis/ Graduation Questionnaire Responses Tufts University School of Medicine, 2006; UA042.001.068.00006 (Box 68)
  - Medical Education Database Sections 1-2 [binder] Tufts University School of Medicine, 2006; UA042.001.068.00007 (Box 68)
  - Medical Education Database Sections 3-5 [binder] Tufts University School of Medicine, 2006; UA042.001.068.00008 (Box 68)
  - NCAA Retention Rates, 1993 -- 2002; UA042.001.068.00009 (Box 68)
  - Old Retirement Survey, 1983 -- 2002; UA042.001.068.00010 (Box 68)
  - Overheads for Trustees Presentation, 1992; UA042.001.068.00011 (Box 68)
  - Rape Survey, 1990; UA042.001.068.00012 (Box 68)
  - Report on the Resident Student Survey [binder] (1 of 3), 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.068.00013 (Box 68)